ISAMU ISOZAKI

BACKEND DEVELOPER OR MACHINE LEARNING DEVELOPER

CAREER OBJECTIVE

Focused Computer Science major (3.98 GPA) currently attending Drexel University, with 1+ years of work experience. Aiming to leverage a proven knowledge of Database design, Website design, and Machine learning skills to successfully fill the Backend Developer or Machine Learning Developer role at your company. Praised as hard-working by my peers, I can be relied upon to help your company achieve its goals.

EXPERIENCE

BACKEND DEVELOPER

Kiara, Shibuya, Tokyo / Jul 2020 - Present

- Setup mail server on Aws so that mail can be recieved
- Processed and translated mails sent to mail server using milters and Node Js with MongoDB

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Kiara, Shibuya, Tokyo / Jul 2020 - Present

 Used React Js for the website and firebase for authentication so that users can register

AI INTERN

Team AI, Shibuya, Tokyo / Jun 2019 - Sep 2019

- Finetuned GPT-2 from Open Al to make Joke Generator for a technical demonstration of the company
- Adapted face2face to make a basic Deepfake for CEO for a potential future zoom avatar

PROJECTS

CHESSKATEERS

Feb 2020 - Jun 2020

 As part of the CI101 course at Drexel, made an online multiplayer game with React Js Frontend, Node Js backend, and Unity for the game itself

TACTIC GAME

Nov 2018 - Present

 Made military strategy game with Pymunk and training using OpenAl baseline

- isamu.website@gmail.com
- (267) 285-6836
- 3200 Chestnut St Room 6008, Philadelphia, PA, 19104

EDUCATION

DREXEL UNIVERSITY

GPA: 3.98

Philadelphia, PA

Bachelor of Computer Science Computer Science Candidate (Expected graduation Jun 2024)

Awards & Honors

- Dean's List
- Dean's Scholarship

Extracurricular Activities

- Drexel Al
- ML Reading Group Directed by Dr. Edward Kim

ADDITIONAL SKILLS

Language: Japanese-Native

Programming: C#, Python, Javascript, CSS, HTML

Tools: Git, Unity, VS Code, Atom, AWS, Ionos, Vim, MongoDb Atlas

Frameworks: Tensorflow, Keras, Pytorch, Numpy, Pandas, React Native, React Js, Mongoose

Operating Systems: Windows, Ubuntu

CERTIFICATIONS

Udacity Frontend Development Nanodegree